We'll be right back.
Superior, huh?
All right, Chief. Go ahead.
Hot, hot! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I spilled coffee all over myself!
Damn it!
Stupid coffee!
What the heck?
So, you're still alive.
Greetings, Cutty Flam.
Long time no see.
It's hard to believe you somehow managed to survive the accident.
Hard to believe.
But good news nonetheless.
Is that so?
Who are you?
Don't you remember me?
I'm the man from Cypher Pool number five
that arrested Tom's workers when I caught them red-handed
for savagely attacking the judicial ship eight years ago.
You're that Sponda guy, aren't you?
Spondam!
You're missing the M!
But I'll have plenty of time to drill that into your head
once you arrive at Eni's lobby.
Make it quick, Ben.
I'm simply dying to teach that criminal a lesson.
Huh?
Damn stupid lamp!
Tie him up.
Ow!
Hey, punk!
Watch those hands!
Come on.
Let him go!
Come back here, you bastards!
I'm sorry.
Hey!
If you're not gonna help, then don't get my hoops up!
Wait, I know you, don't I?
You're part of the Straw Hat crew.
Huh?
Don't any of the
The Truth Behind Her Betrayal, Robin's Sorrowful Decision.
Last train of the day is cutting it kind of close.
Wonder what the government's got in mind.
Dunno, but it must be serious if they're going out during Aqua Lacuna.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
I heard the people getting on tonight are big-shot secret agents.
That's news to me.
Some folks from the Navy were talking about it just a few minutes ago.
From what I gather, the government sent this team of undercover agents to Water 7 a bunch of years ago,
and they just now finished their mission.
Nice timing.
No kidding.
Course I didn't hear the details.
Who knows what they were doing all these years?
And you said these guys were undercover now, didn't you?
That means they might be people we already know.
Actually, you're right.
Now keep this a secret.
But I think I might have a good idea who they are.
Who?
Tell me.
What?
From the back streets?
Mm-hmm.
I've caught them having some real hush-hush conversations in the corner over at Blue Nose Bar.
That might be a little fishy, but I don't think it means they're secret agents.
It's not just that.
They're always spending money and living like kings, even though they hardly work at all.
That's a good point.
I've seen them ride first class quite a few times.
See?
Well, whether I'm right or not, we'll find out their secret identity soon enough.
After all, they'll be boarding the sea train any minute now.
Mark my words, this will be the talk of the whole town tomorrow.
I'm sure.
Oh, yeah.
Iceberg.
Pauly.
Nami.
Oh, no.
I have to treat her right away.
If I can just...
Oh.
Hurry!
They need first aid.
They're burned all over.
Hey, what are we going to do with this reindeer?
Help him.
He's saying they're lies.
You're right.
Hey, someone give me a hand.
Oh, boy.
That's just sad.
So what you're saying is that you left the straw hats, but you haven't given up your life of crime.
What a shame.
If you're a pirate, you're coming with us.
Khalifa?
Got it.
And as for this ship, you still haven't disposed of it?
Stay away!
Don't you dare touch her!
Are you listening to me?
What are you doing?
Even if it was only a temporary disguise, we are still respected as shipwrights.
When we say your ship's done for, then you would do well to listen to us.
What do you care?
It's not even your ship.
I can do whatever I want with it.
This lever releases the water, right?
Cut it out.
That's not funny, damn it.
Hey!
No, stop it!
Don't let her fall!
Don't worry.
I'll carry everyone for a little bit longer.
Mary!
Get back!
I'll cover me!
I'll cover!
You idiot, run!
Dammit!
Is there anything we can do?
Look!
Mr. Iceberg's awake!
All right!
He's safe!
I knew he'd make it!
Hey!
Go, go!
Ah!
That reindeer saved his life!
Are you sure?
I thought it belonged to the Straw Hats!
Hey!
Look!
This woman's from the Straw Hats, too!
So, what now?
Do you think maybe we should tie her up and question her?
I don't know.
She's just a girl.
And she's hurt, too.
I know, but...
Whoa!
You shouldn't be moving yet, Mr. Iceberg!
Sorry, men.
But I need a little space right now.
That is to say,
I want to speak to this woman in private.
Huh?
I wonder what those two are talking about.
Beats me!
What was that for?
Stop standing, man!
Give me a hand!
I know Iceberg and Polly are safe,
but the rest of the foreman might still be trapped inside!
Yeah, he's right.
Let's go!
Oh, but...
Yeah, sorry!
Well...
First off,
I must apologize.
I falsely accused your entire crew.
I'll try to clear that up soon.
But for now,
I want to talk about Nico Robin.
What do you know?
When you first came to Water 7,
did she start acting strangely?
Yeah, she did.
She went into town that day
and then never came back.
But the next morning,
she was the prime suspect
in your attempted murder.
When Sanji and Chopper finally saw her again,
she said this was goodbye
and wouldn't be a part of the crew anymore.
Of course, none of that made any sense to us,
so we decided to break into your mansion
in hopes that we'd be able to see her one more time
and find out the truth.
I did it to make my wish come true.
One that can't happen as long as we're together.
If you can't accept that, I'm sorry.
What kind of wish would force her
to give up all of her friends?
I think I know the answer, actually.
This probably started shortly
after you lost sight of her for the first time.
CP9.
The government had begun its operation
the moment she arrived.
In other words,
there's a good reason
why your friend did what she did.
But before I go into the details,
I want you to understand
that both Nico Robin and I
have the means to revive an ancient weapon
that is capable of destroying the entire world.
A weapon?
That's right.
It's me.
We've hit a snag in the plan.
Everyone head to the bedroom immediately.
Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
Do you understand now?
The blueprints that they found
are fake.
I don't care.
I would rather die
than hand over that information
to the government.
But now it's not that simple.
If you've decided
that you're going to help them
and you're searching
for the Ponyglyphs yourself,
then I have to do everything
I can to stop you.
I understand your concern,
but I'm only studying the Ponyglyphs
to learn more about the history of the world.
I don't care about the weapon.
You have to take responsibility.
I told you this would happen,
but you don't listen.
Frankie,
even if you weren't trying to,
weapons are made to hurt people.
Whether you want them to or not,
they can hurt your friends.
Even if you don't have malicious intent,
your actions can still hurt people.
If your curiosity for history
leads to the destruction of the world,
then you're better off dying
right here and right now,
Nico Robin.
Even after seeing what happened
to the devils of Ohara,
you still want to walk this path?
You don't know a damn thing about Ohara!
You have no idea
how much the world government
has warped my life.
Do you hear me?
If you hate the government so much,
then why help them?
Because I have a wish
that I would sacrifice anything for.
When I came to this town,
CP-9 presented me with two conditions.
The first was to pin your assassination
on the Straw Hats
and leave their crew.
The second was to turn myself
over to the government
and follow their every order
without question.
You realize they won't let you live.
You escaped them for 20 years.
Why would you agree
to something like that now?
In this particular instance,
CP-9 has been given permission
to activate a buster call
against the Straw Hats.
A buster call?
It's an emergency order
that summons five vice admirals
and ten battleships
to the same location.
No matter how strong you are,
no one can survive
a full-scale military attack
of that caliber.
Under normal circumstances,
only the three admirals
and the head of the Navy,
the fleet admiral,
are allowed to exercise
that kind of authority.
However,
this is a special case.
Just this once,
Admiral Aokiji
has given CP-9
the right to make the call.
When I heard his name,
I surrendered.
If I hadn't agreed
to their conditions,
then me and the rest
of the Straw Hats
would have been annihilated.
For the past 20 years,
I've been able to run away
and survive,
no matter what the circumstance.
But that's only because
I had nothing to protect.
Because I was willing
to betray others
and use them as a shield.
But not now.
For the first time
in all these years,
I can't do that.
They picked up
the life I gave up on,
returned the heart I lost,
and continued the dreams
that I no longer believed in.
Even after all I've done,
I've found friends
who will still believe in me.
I see.
But then what is your wish?
That excluding me,
all of the other Straw Hat Pirates
will be allowed
to leave this island safely!
And as long as you have that,
you don't care what happens
to the rest of the world?
I don't!
夢見た僕らは間違いじゃないと信じて 荒く埋れる海原を渡って行ける
誰よりも勇敢で思いやりもあるけれど
もしも君がこの船を降りて 違う世界にいたとしても
最後にはきっと笑えるよ
luffyとZoroをお自らに 今回避けるとすわ
それはetinose5のusi6は1に脱付したイディストにして アンダーをごめんなさい
The steam whistle forces friends apart.
The sea train starts to run.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!